何で…。 やめろよ…
Something is skilled at destroying,
but fixing isn't her forte.
分かったの？ 何　聞いてんだよ… 時間です。
When she's fixing, she must touch the target,
or her power won't work.
利息がつきます。
I will save both Gon and Alluka!
テレパシー あぁ…　うっ…　あぁ！
Impossible... There's no way I can remove this!
テレパシー 待って…　まだ早い！
My power is not enough
黙れ！
to bear this burden.
余は　空腹じゃ。
I'm not talking about taking a crazy gamble.
馳走を用意せい。
In fact, I can guarantee Gon will be healed.
こ…　これが…　王 ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
Let me take care of this. This method isn't as risky as using a Nen exorcist.
テレパシー ゴフっ！ あっ！
But the problem is how I can get there.
女王様！ いかん！ 内臓が　かなり損傷しておる！
This time, that will be the biggest challenge.
あっ。
Wh-What do you—
あっ…。
Not true.
２度　言わせるな 馳走を用意せい。
You said you could guarantee Gon would be healed. That was a reference to Master Alluka's power.
ここは　薄汚いな。
At the moment, you are still
just within Zoldyck property, but outside the boundaries, you are already
at alert level 4, so please be careful.
おい！ はっ。
Level 4...
拭け。
Looks like I pissed off my father.
オッホッホッホッ。 おやおや　私め ちょうど　ハンケチを 持っており…。
If a restriction is violated, the target will immediately be
captured and returned home, and the alert will automatically increase to level 5.
２度　言わすな。 お前だ　拭け。
At level 5, the moment a single step is
taken outside Zoldyck property, the target is captured.
くっ…。 まずい。 うっ…！
First, to protect family secrets, the target may not speak to, or exchange items with,
any outsiders without permission.
あっ…。
To enforce this, the target is forbidden
to carry any communication devices.
飯は　どこだ？
I've already had everything taken away.
お食事のご用意ができております。
Second, to protect family secrets, the target must stay within one meter
of Master Alluka at all times.
これからは 私ども３人が　王の手足となり…。
Yeah, yeah. I don't plan on letting her out of my sight.
王の望むもの　全て手に入れ…。
Third, to protect family secrets, you are forbidden from letting any outsiders
何なりと お申しつけくださいませ。
learn anything about Alluka's power. I understand perfectly.
うむ。
So basically...
早く！　女王様を！ とにかく　止血だ！
While we're traveling, I'll let you
handle all the arrangements! I understand why I am here.
どうだ？　容体は？
Alluka's a girl.
ひどいな　かなり悪い。
I can't trust a lump like you to take care of her!
複数の臓器が 我々の通常の治療では
There is nothing to worry about.
このままだと…。 くっ…。
We shall also accompany you.
ネフェルピトー殿！
that two butlers would be enough.
女王のお命が危ない！
Tsubone!
彼はねぇ　僕にとって必要だから やったことなんだ。 王が生まれちゃったらさぁ
Dad really is pissed... It's fine. I won't do anything stupid at alert level 4.
彼女は　僕らには関係ないんだ。
Listen to me, Killua-chan.
あっ…。 あれは　もう　いらない。
I'm not as lenient as your father and Gotoh. A single violation, and I'll take you home.
女王様！ 女王様！　女王様！
If you resist, I'll knock you out. Keep that in mind.
どうだ？ ネフェルトピトー殿は　お力を？
Yes! Yes! Yes!
ダメだ　あの方…　いや
Tsubone-sensei is the only person
あいつらは　女王を見限った！ 見限った!?
in the entire household who
calls Master Killua "Killua-chan."
女王の命は 俺達が救うしかない！ 無理だ！　さっきも言っただろう
No bullying Brother.
我々の力では あそこまで損傷した
I'm sorry...
女王の臓器を修復することは…。
Alluka-chama is so kind.
奴らなら　できるかもしれない。
I won't do it again. I just realized something.
「奴ら」って？　おい　どこへ行く!?
I have trouble dealing with old ladies.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
Do you love your big brother? I love him lots!
ならば 外から行くほうが早かろう。
Master Killua is depending on me.
お見事。
I will help him! Even if it costs me this job
それ　いいな　んんっ！
Yes, absolutely.
プッ！
Unless I change my mind.
まずい。 お口に　合いませんか？
Do you understand what I mean?
うむ　ひどく薄いな。 もともと 味付けなどしておりませんので。 いや　そういうことではない。
Of course, I will remain near you at all times.
あの女の腹の中で　ごく　まれに
I still have more requests...
非常に濃厚芳醇な馳走が 送られて来たのだ。
She pulled a fast one!
あ レアもののことでございますね。
It's all right. I still have a chance.
あの　えもいえぬ充足感。 余の体が欲しておるわ。
I won't be able to make a wish,
but I can issue a command!
かしこまりました　では…。
Brother, are you angry?
ん？
It's okay.
１匹　真っすぐ　こっちに来るぞ。 気づかれたか？　隠れるぞ。 待て！
There's nothing for you to worry about. I will save you!
白旗？
Yes? Yes.
我々は　降参する！
This is Master Killua's phone.
我々は降参する ただし　条件がある。 女王を助けてやってくれ！
In that case, you should state your name first.
もう妃に　子を産む力はない。
Goodbye. Who was that?
女王を？
It was...
すでに　王は生まれた！
Hello?
くっ…。
My name is Leorio!
奴は…。
Wow, that brings back memories!
奴らは…
It has been quite some time, Master Leorio. Huh?
悪魔だ。
Oh! I remember!
んっ？
Yes, to help Master Gon.
何だ？　こいつらは。
You should know that the Zoldyck
family is very special.
まるで　手応えがなかったぞ。
We are the ones who set the conditions. So shut up and listen, fool.
まずい　ハズレだ。
Please excuse me. Let me talk to him.
人の最も美味な部位が脳みそです。
It'll be faster that way. Don't worry.
故に　頭部を傷つけずに 仕留めるのがよろしいかと。
I won't say anything I'm not supposed to. One violation, and I'll be sent home, right?
さようか。
Yo, it's been a while. Killua!
こうか？
Do as Gotoh says.
なるほど…　悪くない。 だが…　プッ。
This is my phone, and I'm talking to my buddy, so why should I let you talk?
食うには値せぬ。
An excellent question.
レアものに比べればな。
The answer is to give me the phone.
おそれながら申し上げます。
No way. Get lost.
レアものを 見分ける方法がございます。
Very well.
それを使えば…。
Then, I have a favor to ask.
余を愚弄するか。
My guess is that you'll say, "That isn't possible."
目を凝らせば 体を包むエネルギーが
In which case, you should hand over the phone.
見えることくらい 承知しておるわ。 その多寡で判断するのであろうが。
Because I can make it possible.
大変　失礼いたしました。
No, it's nothing. Tell me the conditions.
ただ見つけて食うだけでは 芸がなかろう。 レアかどうか 食うまで分からぬところが興。
When we arrive, there must be no one inside
the building except Master Gon.
腹は　そこそこ満ちておるしな。
Not even doctors? Correct.
時に　ピトーよ。
Or any other patients? Correct.
お主　なかなか強いな 殺すつもりで　やったのだぞ。
That isn't possible!
褒めて遣わす。
This is a national hospital!
もったいないお言葉。
Do you have any idea how
many people are in here?!
部下を…　仲間を食いやがった。
Hello? I understand the conditions.
そいつは間違いだな
Leave it to me. What is the plan?
あれは　俺達と 全然　別の生きものだ。
This is a big hospital, with a big parking lot.
おそらく 自分以外の生物は　全部　餌さ。
We'll set up a private room for Gon there. It'll be arranged so you can
drive in and out of the area.
どうするとは？
I'll make sure that no one can learn
このまま　女王様が死ねば ここにいる意味がなくなるぜ。
what you do inside. Understood.
フッハハハ…。 もう　すでに 意味ねえんじゃねぇか？
That satisfies our requirements. What is your name?
女王には　もう 生殖能力はないんでしょ？ なっ…！
I'm Morel. From now on, I'd like you to
be the one I speak with.
それもそうか。 あっ…！
There you go.
もう　女王に 王国をつくることは不可能。
Oh, I need to make another call.
ならば　俺達　それぞれが 王を目指すべきだろう？
Knov? It's me.
俺達は　好きにやるぜ。
The situation's changed.
お前　自分が何言ってるか 分かってんのか!?
I need you to make sure the equipment
is operable in an outside room.
そんな勝手が許されると思うか!?
No, no monitors.
俺達だけじゃねえぜ　きっと。
And we can't have any windows.
ここを出たいと考えてるのはよ。
True... It sounds like they have a Nen exorcist, since they don't want anyone watching.
お…　お前達！ フッ。
But Killua said he could heal him with no risks.
ようやく分かったか？
No, let's not pursue the matter.
どっちが少数派かってことがよ。
Killua said to let him take care of it.
頼む　時間がないんだ！ 女王が死ねば
In the field, the rule is to listen when
a trusted friend tells you to.
具体的には　どうなる？ おそらく　王のまね事…。
Morel, I'll let you handle all contact with Killua.
野に出て国をつくり 自らの種をばらまく。
Yeah, I've got it. What are you going to do?
指揮系統が崩壊すれば 兵隊長クラスからも 多数　出るだろう。
There are several people
そいつらが世界中へ散って 生態系を荒らす。
I need to have a word with.
女王アリを中心とした コロニーでは
Gon's fighting for his life...
兵は　生殖行為を行いませんが
Where are you, and what are you doing?
女王が死ぬと　兵は巣から散って その能力をフルに発揮することが 報告されています。
Why won't you answer your phone, Kurapika?
お前さん　名前は？ コルト。
And so, the Zodiacs respect the
former chairman's wishes.
俺達のボスのとこへ連れて行く。
And we've worked diligently to maintain
今と同じ話をあんたの口から ボスにしてくれ。
the status quo, and we seek
to better the Association.
ただし　その結果 ボスが　あんたを信じるかどうかは 分からない。 話自体は信じても
Your vote, no matter for whom
you vote, will not go to waste!
ボスが　あんたを 生かして帰す保証は全くない。
You can be assured of that.
それでも　行くかい？
At the same time, I'm sure that some people are dissatisfied
無論だ　一刻も早く頼む！
with the current state of the Association,
or want to shake up the leadership.
事とは　重なるものですね。
However, I must ask that you do not express that opinion
by refusing to cast a vote.
今日は　弟子達の決着がつく日。 おっと　忘れてたぜ。
You are more than welcome to make
a speech up here, on the spot.
俺は　ナックルとシュートの２人に １０万…。
All you have to do is speak up.
お前は　５人全員が来るに １００万だったな。
We will never seek to smother a minority opinion.
ナックル。 あっ？
The entire Association should
work together to clear it!
約束だよ！　カイトを…
Please return to your seat. Make it quick.
カイトを絶対　助けてね！
We now open the floor to everyone here.
任せとけ　必ず連れて戻る。 この割り符に誓ってな。
If you'd like to express your views or
ask a question, raise your hand.
俺　弱いね。
Okay, let's hear the answer. First, what is your relationship to Gon?
俺…　思わなかった。
That's all. Answer my question! Or just go visit him!
弱いことが…
Do you have any idea how much
Gon wants to see you?
こんなに悔しいなんて 思わなかった。
If you talk to him, he might recover!
お前が 「念」を使えない３０日間
You can go to hell!
俺が　お前を守るよ
Wow!
どんなことをしても 何に代えても それが　過ぎたら…
You'll find footage of today's entire
meeting on the Hunter site, so tell everyone who wasn't present!
お別れだ
Tell them they absolutely have to watch it!